netjets.com 2017-02-20

# NetJets Privacy Policy

NetJets Inc. and our affiliated companies NetJets Aviation, Inc., NetJets Europe, , Executive Jet Management, and Marquis Jet Partners, Inc. (collectively "NetJets"), respect your privacy. This Privacy Policy ("Policy") outlines the information NetJets collects from visitors to our websites in an effort to support and further our relationship with you, including providing you with requested information and/or products or services. We do not sell or rent your personal information.

This Policy also describes the personal information we may collect about you, how we may use and disclose that information and the choices you can make about how we collect and use your information. You may at any time contact NetJets with any privacy questions or concerns you may have by clicking here to contact NetJets via email. You also may ask at any time to see the personal data we have on file for you and request a correction or deletion.

NetJets encourages you to read this Policy before using any of our websites or submitting any personal data. Your use of any of our websites signifies that you agree to our processing of personal data as described in this Policy and that you agree to all of the terms of this Policy. Please do not use our websites if you disagree with any part of this Policy.

**What kind of information does NetJets collect?**

**Technical Information:**  
NetJets utilizes third-party tracking applications to measure and analyze site traffic. These applications may collect information such as your computer’s operating system and browser type, IP address, address of a referring website, if any, etc. and may track a user’s path through our websites.

**Personal Information:**  
Except as set forth in this Policy, NetJets will not through its websites collect, store or release any personal identifying information about you without first receiving your consent. If you visit this website or if you affirmatively contact NetJets and request information, you are consenting to NetJets' collection of information about you such as your name, title, company, email address, mailing address, phone numbers, flight preferences, and requirements.

The NetJets store and other NetJets' websites may offer you the opportunity to purchase branded merchandise online. In connection with those purchases, you may be asked to submit personal information, such as shipping address and credit card information that is required to complete the transaction. Credit card data will be protected by Secure Sockets Layer ("SSL") or other encryption mechanisms.

**How does NetJets use my information?**

When you request information from NetJets, the information you provide will be kept confidential and will be used to fulfill your request. We may also send you an email to confirm your request and may need to contact you via phone, postal mail or email if we have other questions regarding your request. When you register with NetJets you may receive emails from us regarding our products, services, contests, and promotions. From time to time, we may also send you emails to help us learn more about your purchasing preferences. In addition, we may use information about your product interests and purchases to help us improve our website design and your purchasing experience. NetJets will also disclose personal information if required by law, including compliance with warrants, subpoenas or other legal process.

**Does NetJets share my information with third parties?**

We may contract with third parties to assist us in collecting, maintaining and managing our website visitor information, to fulfill subscriptions and other requests and/or to communicate with our website visitors. We do not authorize any of those third parties to make any other use of your information. NetJets requires third parties to which it discloses personal information to restrict their use of such information to the purposes for which it has been provided by NetJets and not to disclose that information to others. NetJets cannot be responsible, however, for any damages caused by the failure of unaffiliated third parties to honor their privacy obligations to NetJets.

Additionally, NetJets may share personal information with other companies, lawyers, credit bureaus, agents or government agencies in the following cases: (1) when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact, or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) the rights of NetJets or to anyone that could be harmed by such activities; (2) when we believe in good faith that the law requires it; (3) to our parent company or to any third party who may acquire NetJets; and (4) in situations involving threats to the physical safety of any person.

**How do I access and update my information?**

You can contact NetJets at 877-356-5823 or [headquarters@netjets.com](mailto:headquarters@netjets.com), to determine if we are keeping personal information about you. If we do have personal information about you, we will provide you with a readable copy of such personal information at no charge. Factual errors in your personal information, including information that is out of date, can be corrected by sending us a request that sufficiently details how your personal information should be corrected. We encourage you to promptly update your personal information if it changes.

**How do I remove my information from email and postal mailing lists?**

If at any time you would like us to update your personal information or remove you from our email or postal mailing lists, feel free to contact us by sending an email to headquarters@netjets.com. Please be sure to include your email address, and full name.

We want to communicate with you only if you want to hear from us. You may at any time opt-out of receiving communications from us. If you prefer not to receive information from us, either through email or regular mail, please let us know by sending an email to [headquarters@netjets.com](mailto:headquarters@netjets.com), responding directly to an email you have received, or by clicking an opt-out link. Please note that such requests may take up to 2-3 weeks to become effective. If you request that we not include you on our email or postal mailing lists, we will use reasonable efforts to ensure that we honor your request.

**What is a “cookie” and does NetJets place it on my computer?**

When you access many websites, information may be stored on your computer in the form of a "cookie" or similar file that is saved in your computer's browser. NetJets does not store any personal information in cookies. All personal information is stored separately on its secured servers.

**How does NetJets protect my personal information?**

You can be assured that personal information collected through the websites is secure and is maintained in a manner consistent with current industry standards. The importance of security for all personal information associated with our subscribers is of utmost concern to us. Your personal information is protected in several ways. Your personal information resides on a secure server that only select NetJets staff and contractors have access to via password. We encrypt your personal information and thereby prevent unauthorized parties from viewing such information when it is transmitted to us. In order to most efficiently serve you, credit card transactions and order fulfillment are handled by established third-party banking, processing agents and distribution institutions. They receive the information needed to verify and authorize your credit card or other payment information and to process and ship your order. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, you acknowledge that: (a) there are security and privacy limitations of the internet which are beyond our control; (b) the security, integrity, and privacy of any and all information and data exchanged between you and us through the websites cannot be guaranteed; and (c) any such information and data may be viewed or tampered with in transit by a third party. If you do not want to provide your personal information to NetJets over the Internet, please contact NetJets at 877-356-5823 or in writing at: NetJets, 4111 Bridgeway Avenue, Columbus, Ohio 43219.

**NetJets’ Commitment to Children’s Privacy**

NetJets takes children's privacy seriously. We never collect or maintain information at our websites from persons we know to be under age 13, and no part of our websites are designed to attract anyone under age 13. Please do not communicate with or contact us if you are under age 13.

**Changes to Policy**

As we continue to develop our websites and take advantage of new technologies to improve the sites, this Policy will likely change. NetJets reserves the right to change, modify, or amend this Policy at any time without prior notice to you. We therefore encourage you to refer to this Policy on an ongoing basis so that you understand its current terms. Information on material changes to this Policy will be posted on NetJets' websites for thirty (30) days. NetJets may also let you know of the Policy change by communicating directly with you.

If you do not accept a changed version of this Policy (for example, if you do not approve of a different way that we intend to use personal information) you may let us know by letter or e-mail. If you do not send us any objections, we will assume that you consent to changes in the Policy. Changes will not apply retroactively to personal information that was collected before the changes to the Policy, except as may be required by law. If you have any questions about this Policy, you may contact us by mail at NetJets, 4111 Bridgeway Avenue, Columbus, Ohio 43219 or by e-mail at [headquarters@netjets.com](mailto:headquarters@netjets.com).

**Third Party Sites**

NetJets' websites may contain links to other sites that are not operated by NetJets. Please be aware that these sites may collect information about you. NetJets is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content on any websites that it does not operate. To ensure protection of your privacy, always review the privacy policies of those sites you visit.
